- We do?
- Uh-huh. Look.
(Leonard:)Mrs. Fiona Fondell from
Huntsville, Alabama has ordered two.
- No kidding. Two?
- Uh-huh. Look at the comments.
"Thank you, Penny Blossoms.
These'll be perfect to cover my bald spots."
(Howard:)Aw.
Yeah. That is so sweet.
(Sheldon:)Camouflaging bald spots.
That's primarily a male concern.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps we could expand our market.
(Penny:)How are flower barrettes
gonna appeal to men?
- We add Bluetooth.
- Oh.
- Brilliant. Men love Bluetooth.
PENNY: Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You wanna make a hair barrette
with Bluetooth?
(Sheldon:)Penny, everything is better
with Bluetooth.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
(Leonard:)Holy crap. Someone just ordered
1000 Penny Blossoms.
Get out! Who needs 1000
sparkly flower barrettes with rhinestones?
"The fifth annual East Rutherford,
New Jersey, Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual...